CAITLIN BISHOP

Orlando, FL
Phone: (757)353-5711 | Email: bishopce16@gmail.com
LinkedIn: | GitHub

Summary

Data Analyst with a passion for learning. Earned a certificate from the University of Central Florida Data Analytics and Visualization Bootcamp. 5+ years of experience in customer service and sales. Insatiable intellectual curiosity and strengths in analytical problem solving. Adept at working independently and collaborating with teams.

Technical Skills

Languages: Python, CSS, R, JavaScript ES6+, HTML, SQL, NoSQL

Applications: GitHub, MongoDB, APIs, PostgreSQL, pgAdmin, AWS, Flask, Command Line,

Tableau

Tools: Excel, VBA, TensorFlow, Databasing, Pandas, Leaflet, Plotly, Jupyter Notebook

Projects

mission-to-mars | https://github.com/bishopce16/Mission-to-Mars.git

- A web-scraping project using various tools to build a web application to scrape different websites for data related to the mission to mars and present the data and images on a single page.
- Visual Studio Code, Anaconda, Jupyter Notebook, Python, HTML, BeautifulSoup, Splinter, MongoDB, Webdriver_Manager, PyMongo, Flask Application, Datetime, Pandas.

surfs_up | https://github.com/bishopce16/surfs_up.git

- The purpose of this analysis is to determine the potential success of opening a surf and ice cream (Surf n Shakes) shop by analyzing weather data for the Island of Oahu, HI.
- Python, SQLite, SQLAlchemy, Visual Studio Code, Jupyter Notebook, Pandas, Numpy, Matplotlib, Anaconda, Dateframe_image.

Pewlett-Hackard-Analysis https://github.com/bishopce16/kickstarter-analysis-.git

- The purpose of this project was to analyze human resources data for a large company (Pewlett-Hackard) to help the company prepare for the future hiring demands.
- Python, Visual Studio Code, pgAdmin 4.

Stock Analysis | https://github.com/bishopce16/stock-analysis.git

- Using Visual Basic Application or VBA to analyze green stock for Steve, to discover which stocks are worth the investment for his parents.
- Python, Microsoft Excel, Visual Basic Application (VBA), Visual Studio Code.

Election Analysis | https://github.com/bishopce16/Election_Analysis.git

- The Colorado Board of Elections requested help to complete an election audit for a recent local congressional election.
- Python, Visual Studio Code.

Experience

Merchandise Expert/Receiver

2021 - Present

Super Target SODO Store #2376

Orlando, FL

- Mentored new employees on company procedures and safety standards.
- Accepting and managing vendor orders.
- Prioritize projects based on team and store needs.
- Certified equipment operator.
- Managed inventory and facilitated vendor relationships.

Merchandise/Fulfillment Expert

2019 - 2021

Pembroke Target Store #2770

Virginia, VA

- Mentored new employees on company procedures and safety standards.
- Certified equipment operator.
- Implemented new merchandise displays that lowered restucking time.
- Fulfillment specialist maintaining inventory on and off the sales floor and completing online and in-store order in an efficient and timely manner.

Logistics/Fulfillment Expert

2016 - 2019

Roanoke, VA

- **Roanoke Target Store #1162**
 - Mentored new employees on company procedures and safety standards.
 - Implemented new merchandise displays that lowered restucking time.
 - Fulfillment specialist maintaining inventory on and off the sales floor and completing online and in-store order in an efficient and timely manner.
 - Certified equipment operator.

Laboratory Assistant Hollins University

2015 - 2016

Roanoke, VA

- Managed the scheduling and logistics of the laboratory and researchers.
- Conducted research under the laboratory supervisor.
- Maintained laboratory supplies, cleanliness, and safety.
- Provided care, handling, and feeding of over 30 different reptiles.

Education

Data Analytics and Visualization Bootcamp Certificate: University of Central Florida, Orlando, FL

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in Excel, VBA, Python, R, JavaScript, SQL Databases, Tableau, Big Data, and Machine Learning.

Bachelor of Arts in Biology: Hollins University, Roanoke, VA

A general biology degree that cultivated a sense of independent inquiry into the processes of life with a solid foundation in the biological sciences (from cells to ecosystems). While promoting the development of strong oral and written communication skills as well as critical thinking.